<?xml version="1.0"?> <feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>GLFW - An OpenGL library</title><link href="http://www.glfw.org/"/><link rel="self" href="http://www.glfw.org/feed/index.xml" type="application/atom+xml"/> <updated>2016-06-02T16:46:47+02:00</updated> <id>http://www.glfw.org/</id> <author> <name>elmindreda</name> <email>webmaster@glfw.org</email> </author> <entry> <id>http://www.glfw.org//Version-3.2-released</id><link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://www.glfw.org/Version-3.2-released.html"/><title>Version 3.2 released</title> <updated>2016-06-02T00:00:00+02:00</updated> <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;GLFW 3.2 is &lt;a href="download.html"&gt;available for download&lt;/a&gt;. It adds support for Vulkan surface creation, window mode switching, window maximization, window input focus control, window size and aspect ratio limits, human-readable key names, window icons, joystick connection events, XInput and DirectInput joystick input, event waiting with timeout, 64-bit integer raw timer, context-less window creation, run-time context creation API selection, adds simpler build-time configuration, improved documentation and fixes for a large number of bugs that together affect all supported platforms.&lt;/p&gt;</content> </entry> <entry> <id>http://www.glfw.org//Version-3.1.2-released</id><link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://www.glfw.org/Version-3.1.2-released.html"/><title>Version 3.1.2 released</title> <updated>2015-10-12T00:00:00+02:00</updated> <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;GLFW 3.1.2 is &lt;a href="download.html"&gt;available for download&lt;/a&gt;. It adds fixes for a large number of bugs that together affect all supported platforms, as well as dynamic loading work that simplifies compilation and linking.&lt;/p&gt;</content> </entry> <entry> <id>http://www.glfw.org//Version-3.1.1-released</id><link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://www.glfw.org/Version-3.1.1-released.html"/><title>Version 3.1.1 released</title> <updated>2015-03-19T00:00:00+01:00</updated> <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;GLFW 3.1.1 is &lt;a href="download.html"&gt;available for download&lt;/a&gt;. It adds fixes for a number of bugs that together affect all supported platforms, most notably workarounds for bugs in some popular window managers.&lt;/p&gt;</content> </entry> <entry> <id>http://www.glfw.org//Version-3.1-released</id><link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://www.glfw.org/Version-3.1-released.html"/><title>Version 3.1 released</title> <updated>2015-01-18T00:00:00+01:00</updated> <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;GLFW 3.1 is &lt;a href="download.html"&gt;available for download&lt;/a&gt;. It adds improved documentation, support for custom system cursors, file drop events, main thread wake-up, window frame size retrieval, floating windows, character input with modifier keys, single buffered windows, build improvements and fixes for a large number of bugs.&lt;/p&gt;</content> </entry> <entry> <id>http://www.glfw.org//Version-3.0.4-released</id><link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://www.glfw.org/Version-3.0.4-released.html"/><title>Version 3.0.4 released</title> <updated>2013-12-31T00:00:00+01:00</updated> <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;GLFW 3.0.4 is available for download. It adds fixes for a number of bugs that together affect all supported platforms, most notably MinGW compilation issues and cursor mode issues on OS X.&lt;/p&gt;</content> </entry> <entry> <id>http://www.glfw.org//Pandora</id><link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://www.glfw.org/Pandora.html"/><title>Pandora: First Contact</title> <updated>2013-11-20T00:00:00+01:00</updated> <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://pandora.proxy-studios.com/"&gt;Pandora: First Contact&lt;/a&gt; is a science fiction 4X turn-based strategy game on a planetary scale, inspired by Sid Meier’s Alpha Centauri. As the various factions strive to take control, each will research and develop new technologies, discover new weapons and ancient alien ruins, create trade agreements and forge alliances with other factions.&lt;/p&gt; </content> </entry> <entry> <id>http://www.glfw.org//TimeLines</id><link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://www.glfw.org/TimeLines.html"/><title>TimeLines: Assault on America</title> <updated>2013-11-11T00:00:00+01:00</updated> <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://store.steampowered.com/app/234060/"&gt;TimeLines: Assault on America&lt;/a&gt; is a real-time strategy game that attempts to revive and modernize elements of Command &amp;amp; Conquer and Starcraft. It is set in an alternate history after WWII and has the goal of portraying the Central and Eastern Europe armored forces that are still unknown to many.&lt;/p&gt; </content> </entry> <entry> <id>http://www.glfw.org//Version-3.0.3-released</id><link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://www.glfw.org/Version-3.0.3-released.html"/><title>Version 3.0.3 released</title> <updated>2013-09-24T00:00:00+02:00</updated> <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;GLFW 3.0.3 is available for download. It adds fixes for a number of bugs that together affect all supported platforms, most notably MinGW compilation issues and cursor mode issues on OS X.&lt;/p&gt;</content> </entry> <entry> <id>http://www.glfw.org//Version-3.0.2-released</id><link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://www.glfw.org/Version-3.0.2-released.html"/><title>Version 3.0.2 released</title> <updated>2013-08-25T00:00:00+02:00</updated> <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;GLFW 3.0.2 is available for download. It adds support for OpenGL 4 and precise scrolling deltas on OS X and fixes for a number of bugs that together affect all supported platforms.&lt;/p&gt;</content> </entry> <entry> <id>http://www.glfw.org//Version-3.0.1-released</id><link type="text/html" rel="alternate" href="http://www.glfw.org/Version-3.0.1-released.html"/><title>Version 3.0.1 released</title> <updated>2013-06-17T00:00:00+02:00</updated> <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;GLFW 3.0.1 is available for download. It adds fixes for a number of bugs that together affect all supported platforms.&lt;/p&gt; </content> </entry></feed>